Chico, chico, chico, lo sé
Sé que tienes los sentimientos
Oh, tengo tanta curiosidad
Acerca de ti chico, quiero
mantener la calma
Pero, cada vez que te mueves
Me congelo y
Me vuelvo tan tímida
Es obvio
Atrapar los sentimientos
como mariposas
Si digo lo que tengo en mente
¿Acertaría en el blanco?
Dispara
Estoy listo, apunta y dispara
Cariño, yo
Siento que Cupido está vivo
Vivo esta noche
Sí, esta noche
Si tu corazón late de la
misma manera, dímelo
Porque estoy boom boom boom
de pies a cabeza y
Sé que el amor es algo tan curioso
Un encanto misterioso
Tengo que conocerte más
Porque, puedo sentir
una conexión real
Una atracción sobrenatural-ah
Tengo sentimientos por
ti, sí, sí, sí, sí
Me has robado el corazón, oh si
Nunca lo dejes ir oh oh no
Nunca lo dejes ir oh oh oh
Un rayo directo a mi corazón, oh si
I got all the feels for sure
Yeah, I got all the feels for ya
Boy I boy I boy I know
I know I get the feels
I know you feel it too
Sway in the moonlight,
Dance in the dark I
I know that I caught your eye
Are we on, the same vibe I
wonder what's on your mind
Cuz you got me good and
I wanna be ya boo
If it's dumb well I wanna be a fool
Underneath the neon lights bebe
Electricity tonight bebe
I know love it is such a funny thing
A mystery allure
Gotta get to know you more
Cuz I, I can feel a real connection
A supernatural attraction-ah
I got the feels for you
yea yea yea yea
You have stolen my heart, oh yeah
Never let it go oh oh no
Never let it go oh oh oh
Lightning straight to
my heart, oh yeah
I got all the feels for sure
Yeah, I got all the feels for ya
Boy I boy I boy I know
I know I get the feel
I know you feel it too
Boy I boy I boy I know
I know I get the feels
I know you feel it too
You got my attention
So what's your intention
Yeah, tell me baby what's the deal?
Oh, one look and I know
it baby my eyes reveal
That you you you give me the feels
You have stolen my heart, oh yeah
Never let it go oh oh no
Never let it go oh oh oh
Lightning straight to
my heart, oh yeah
I got all the feels for sure
Yeah, I got all the feels for ya
Boy I boy I boy I know
I know I get the feels
I know you feel it too
Boy I boy I boy I know
I know I get the feels
I know you feel it too